All
right. Hello, church family.
Um, we are back. Just put a one in the
chat if you could hear me.
Um, we uh
Wow. Uh, I have
never and I think I've
preached important sermons, but I've
never had as much
um
just chaos happen
um with a message as I have with this
one.
Um, so listen, we're going to we're
going to start this from the top and I
just need you to let people know, hey,
we are back on. Um, we're hoping that
this storm doesn't come back
through. Um, but we're going to go
ahead. We're going to pray again. And,
uh, we're going to start from the top.
We're going to start from the top. So,
um, let's do that. Let's pray. Heavenly
Father, Lord, I ask that you would just
please uh grant us your spirit, Lord.
Um Lord, please speak
again as as I share this message, Lord.
And
um again, may your people hear and
understand is our prayer in Jesus name.
Amen.
Amen. All right, everyone.
Um, again, the title of the message is
three unclean spirits. We're going to be
dealing with the
uh with the idea that the Bible teaches
that there will be a
one world
um government, a one world uniting, if
you will. Everyone is going to come
together. Um, and the question we had it
in mind was how are all the different
political uh how all the different
political factions, how are all the
different religious uh uh um uh
denominations and different religion
backgrounds, how are they all going to
come together in one as the Bible
predicts? We're going to go back to the
screen. We're going to go to the screen.
We're going to open up with Revelation
13:3. Revelation 13:3. The Bible says
here, "And I saw one of his heads as it
were wounded to death, and all the world
wandered after the beast." We see here
that the entire
world is going to wander after the
beast. The entire world is going to
wander after the beast. According to
Revelation
16:13, Revelation 16:13, note what the
Bible says here. It says, 'I saw three
unclean spirits like frogs come out of
the mouth of the dragon and out of the
mouth of the beast and out of the mouth
of the false prophet. For they are
spirits of devils working miracles which
go forth unto the kings of the earth and
of the whole world to gather them to the
battle of the great day of God Almighty.
The Bible tells us here that the way
that the whole world is going to be
gathered together is through these three
unclean spirits like frogs. These
unclean spirits like frogs are going to
be working miracles. They're going to be
working miracles. And so we see here
that it will take a miracle to bring the
entire world together. It's going to
take a miracle to bring all the world
together. So the question now is what
kind of miracle is this going to be?
Note again with me Matthew chapter 24
beginning with verse four. The Bible
says, "And Jesus answered and said unto
them." Jesus answered and said unto
them, "Take heed that no man deceive
you. For many shall come in my name,
saying, I am Christ, and shall
deceive many, shall deceive many.
Matthew
24:4 says, "For there shall arise false
Christ and false prophets, and shall
show great signs and wonders in so much
that if it were possible, they shall
deceive the very elect." So then if we
bring everything together so far we see
that what is going to gather the whole
world
together that the whole world is going
to gather together what's going to
gather the whole world together is uh
what the Bible calls miracles and that
these miracles these miracles are going
to be done in the name of Jesus meaning
they are going to be Christian miracles
or Christlike miracle miracles. Thus,
these miracles will be designed to lead
people to think they are Christian in
nature. And if they deceive the whole
world, it is
because it is because they are deceiving
the world into thinking and believing
something that appears to be Christian.
This lets us know beloved that the
entire world is going to end up
claiming Christianity because the whole
world is going to be deceived. These are
miracles that are of a counterfeit
Christian nature designed to deceive
even if even if it were possible the
very elect. Revelation 18:3. Revelation
18:3. Note what the Bible says here. It
says, "For all nations have drunk of the
wine of the wrath of her fornication,
and the kings of the earth, have
committed fornication with her, and the
merchants of the earth have waxed rich
through the abundance of her
delicacies." The Bible tells us that all
nations, not some nations, all nations,
are going to drink of the wine of the
wrath of her fornication. So all nations
drink of this wine, whatever that is.
All nations are going to be
deceived. And Revelation 18 verse 23
puts this in an even more specific way.
Notice what it says. Revelation 18 and
verse 23. The Bible says uh and the
light of a candle shall shine no more at
all in thee. And the voice of the
bridegroom and of the bride shall be
heard no more at all in thee. For thy
merchants were the great men of the
earth. For by thy
sorceries were all nations deceived. By
thy sorceries were all nations deceived.
So the Bible tells us that what deceives
the nations are sorceries. The Greek
word is pharmarmacia. But if we ask what
is it that that the Bible has just said
is going to bring the whole world
together to deceive the whole world. It
is those frogs. The frogs equal sorcery.
The Greek word for sorcery is
pharmarmacia. And I want you to
understand this word as meaning that
they they are going to be so medicated
upon uh by these sorceries. Mentally
medicated, not physically medicated,
mentally medicated so that they cannot
discern the difference between truth and
error. So why does the Bible mention
frogs? Come back with me to Exodus 7.
Exodus chapter 7. And I want you to
notice with me verse 10. Exodus 7:10.
The Bible says, by the way, this is
speaking of the children of Israel as
they're getting ready to leave Egypt.
And you will note here that the Bible is
about to tell us something about frogs.
We want to know why the Bible is using
frogs in Revelation chapter 18 uh
Revelation 16 to describe the sorcery of
Revelation 18 that is going to deceive
people at the end of time. The Bible
says in in Exodus 7:10 and 11, it says,
"And Moses and Aaron went in unto
Pharaoh, and as they did so, and they
did so as the Lord had commanded, and
Aaron cast down his rod before the
Pharaoh, and before his servants, and it
became a serpent." Then Pharaoh also
called the wise men and the sorcerers.
Now the magicians of Egypt, they also
did like manner in like manner with
their enchantment enchantments. the the
the
the magicians of Pharaoh were able to
counterfeit the miracle of Moses
throwing down his
rod and having that rod turn into a
serpent. So, they were able to
counterfeit this miracle. Notice again
with me uh Exodus 7 21. This is now the
first plague where the fish in the river
died. The Bible says, "And the river
stank, and the Egyptians could not drink
of the water of the river, and they and
there was blood throughout all the land
of Egypt. And the magicians of Egypt did
so with their enchantments, and
Pharaoh's heart was hardened." Once
again, we see here that Pharaoh, his
magicians were able to counterfeit this
miracle. They were able to counterfeit
the miracle. And now, I want you to
notice the third or the second plague,
if you will.
It's found in Exodus 8:1. Exodus 8:1.
Note with me Exodus 8:1. And the Lord
spake unto Moses, "Go unto Pharaoh and
say unto him, thus sayeth the Lord, let
my people go that they may serve me. And
if you refuse to let them go, but
behold, I will smite all thy borders
with frogs.
And the river shall bring forth frogs
abundantly, which shall go up, and come
into thine house, and into thy bed
chamber, and upon thy bed, and into the
house of thy servants, and upon thy
people, and into thy and into thine
ovens, and into thy kneading troughs.
And the frog shall come up both on thee,
and upon thy people, and upon all thy
servants.
Note again with me that this miracle of
the frogs, watch this. Let me keep
reading. Let me keep reading. The Bible
goes on to say verse uh verse
5. And the Lord spake unto Moses, say
unto Aaron, stretch forth thine hand
with a rod over the streams of the
rivers, and over the ponds, and cause
frogs to come upon the land of Egypt.
And Aaron stretched out his hand over
the waters of Egypt. And the frogs came
up and covered the land of Egypt. And
the magicians did so also with their
enchantments and brought up frogs upon
the land. So here's the two things I
want you to see here.
Number one. Number
one, the
magicians were able to
counterfeit the plague, the plague of
the frogs, but it was the last
counterfeit that they could pull off.
After this, they could not counterfeit
any more of the miracles that
God had done through Moses and
Aaron. So now they're no longer
able to counterfeit,
meaning this is the last
counterfeit. The last counterfeit that
they could pull off. Number one. Number
two, uh um note with me according to
Exodus 5:2. When they first go in to
talk to Pharaoh, notice Pharaoh's
disposition. Exodus 5:2, the Bible says,
"And Pharaoh said, "Who is the Lord that
I should obey his voice to let Israel
go? I know not the Lord, neither will I
let Israel go. I know not the Lord,
neither will I let Israel go."
Pharaoh did not
know the Lord.
He rejected the Lord. He was an
unbeliever. But when the plague of the
frogs hit, notice what Pharaoh says.
Exodus 5, Exodus chapter 8 rather,
Exodus chapter 8 verse 8. Then Pharaoh
called from Moses and Aaron and said,
"Entreat the Lord that he may take away
the frogs from me." So what has Pharaoh
now done?
Pharaoh has now moved from
unbeliever to
believer. Pharaoh has now moved from
believer. Yeah. And he was an atheist,
but the miracle of the frogs makes him a
believer.
Now, he's not a believer in heart, but
he believe he's he's mentally asenting.
Okay, there's a
God. What does this tell
us? What this tells us, beloved, is that
the plague of the
frogs did two things or reveals two
things. Number one, this is the last
miracle that Satan will be able to
counterfeit before the coming of Jesus.
And number two, this miracle makes
unbelievers into believers. At the end
of time, there's not going to be
unbelievers and atheists and agnostics
and people of all these different
religions. At the end of time, the frogs
is going to the miracle of the frogs is
going to make
everybody a
believer. Put a one in the chat if you
follow me so
far. So now the question is very simple.
What is the last miracle Satan will be
able to counterfeit which will
convince unbelievers? Let's go back to
the screen. 2 Thessalonians chapter 2:1.
The Bible says, "Now we beseech you,
brethren, by the coming of our Lord
Jesus Christ, and by our gathering
together unto him, that you be not soon
shaken in mind or be troubled, neither
by spirit, nor by word, nor by letter as
from us, as at the day of Christ is at
hand. Let no man deceive you by any
means, for that day shall not come,
except there come a falling away first,
and that man of sin be revealed, the son
of
predition, who has who opposes and
exaltth himself above all that is called
God or that is worshiped, so that he as
God sitth in the temple of God, showing
himself that he is God.
understand what's going on
here. We're told in this verse that just
before Jesus comes again, there's going
to be a revelation of someone who is
sitting who who is claiming to be God.
And in order to claim to be God, it's
going to have to be someone with
supernatural power that will actually be
able to convince people that he is
God. And beloved, this is in
fact the Bible telling
us what that miracle is going to be.
It is going to convince people
unbelievers to become believers. And it
will be the last miracle that Satan can
counterfeit before the second coming of
Christ. Come on, let's go back to the
screen. And I want you to note with
me, note with me. Uh 2 Thessalonians
chapter 8. Then shall that wicked be
revealed, whom the Lord shall consume
with the spirit of his of his mouth, and
shall destroy with the brightness of his
coming, even him whose coming is after
the working of Satan with all power and
signs and lying wonders. We are told
here that whatever this miracle is, it
will be the working of Satan. It will be
the working of Satan. According to
Matthew 24:30, the Bible says, "Then
shall appear the sign of the Son of Man
in heaven, and then shall all the tribes
of the earth mourn, and they shall see
the Son of Man coming in the clouds of
heaven with power and great glory."
So if Jesus is
coming is something that happens with
great power and glory and everybody is
going to see it. I want you to
understand that Satan somehow or another
is going to
attempt to do something miraculous
before Jesus comes again. And please
note with me 2 Corinthians chapter
11:14. The Bible says, "And no marvel,
for Satan himself is transformed into an
angel of light. Therefore, it is no
great thing if his ministers of
righteousness or also be
transformed as ministers of
righteousness whose end shall be
according to their works." So now we're
literally told here that Satan is going
to transform himself into an angel of
light. put this all together. Miracles
are going to be happening. There's going
to be a miracle that occurs just before
Jesus comes again. The miracle will will
convince
unbelievers that God
exists, that God exists. It's going to
be a counterfeit miracle in the name of
Jesus. And it's going to be a miracle
that involves the appearing of a being
who will look like Jesus, who will claim
to be Jesus, who will claim to be God.
But we know that this individual is
Satan himself who is transformed as an
angel of light. Note again with me 1
Thessalonians chapter 14, chapter 4
verse 15. Notice what the Bible says.
For this we say unto you by the word of
the Lord, that we which are alive and
remain until the coming of the Lord
shall not prevent them which are asleep.
For the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with a shout, with the voice of
the archangel, and with the trump of
God, and the dead in Christ shall rise
first. Then we which are alive and
remain shall be caught up together with
them in the clouds to meet the Lord in
the air. And so shall we ever be with
the Lord. So, please note here
that that when when when Jesus comes
again, the Bible says he's coming with
the voice of the archangel. Put the name
of the archangel in the chat for me,
please. The name of the
archangel is Michael.
So, we know that the coming of Jesus is
somehow or another tied in with the
voice of the archangel at which time the
dead shall rise. So, whatever this
miracle is, it's going to happen shortly
before this event with Michael the
archangel. Why is this so important to
understand? Because the same event is
described in the book of
Daniel 12 beginning with verse one. Note
with me Daniel 12:1 the Bible says and
at that time shall Michael stand up the
great prince which standeth for the
children of thy people. And there shall
be a time of trouble such as never was
since there was a nation even to that
same time. And at that time thy people
shall be delivered. Everyone that shall
be found written in the book, and many
of them that sleep in the dust of the
earth shall awake, some to everlasting
life, and some to shame and everlasting
contempt. So Daniel
12 parallels the event that we just read
about in 1 Thessalonians.
Daniel 12 is speaking of the
resurrection of the dead when Michael
stands
up. Thessalonians describes it as the
voice of the
archangel raising the
dead. Now, why am I pointing out Daniel
12 to show this parallel event? Because
one chapter earlier and in fact just
five six verses earlier we read about a
particular power or being called the
king of the north. Come back with me to
Daniel 11 and verse 40. Daniel 11:40 the
Bible says so this is five verses before
Daniel
12:1. It says, "And at that at the time
of the end, the king of the south shall
push at him." Don't worry about who the
king of the south is at the moment, but
I want you to focus on this king of the
north. And the king of the north shall
come against him like a whirlwind and
with chariots and with horsemen and with
many ships and shall enter into the
countries and shall overflow and pass
over.
Okay. So what is this
power or who is this power who is
described as a king of the
north who is going to overflow in these
countries and come against these
countries and come against this other
king like a whirlwind with chariots and
with ships. May I suggest to you that
this king of the north power or
being is the same being
described in sec in uh
Thessalonians which says just before
Jesus comes again this power is going to
sit in the place of God pretending to be
God. May I suggest that just as Daniel
parallels what we've seen in the New
Testament that this king of the north
power that leads up to Michael standing
up is none other than the same
being we are told will sit in the temple
of God showing himself to be
God. Let me make it a even clearer. Let
me make it even clearer. Who is this
king of the north? In the book of Isaiah
chapter 14, in the book of Isaiah
chapter
14:12, you will note speaking the Bible
speaking of
Lucifer, it says, "How art thou fallen
from heaven, oh Lucifer, son of the
morning? How art thou cut down to the
ground which did weaken the nations? For
thou has said in thine heart, I will
ascend into heaven. I will exalt my
throne above the stars of God. I will
sit also upon the mount of the
congregation in the sides of the north.
I will ascend above the heights of the
clouds. I will be like the most
high. I will be like the most
high. Lucifer
himself in heaven wanted the place and
position of God. As a result of that, he
was kicked out of
heaven. At the very end of
time, Lucifer himself, Satan
himself, will attempt to do exactly what
he did in heaven on
earth. Meaning, he will seek to take the
place of God. This is the being that is
being
described as appearing just before the
Lord himself
comes. In
fact, the Hebrew word here for I will be
like is the word dama. And I want you to
note what the word
means. It means to com. It means by
implication to resemble.
Put that word in the chat for me,
everyone. To
resemble.
Resemble. This being is going to seek to
resemble the most high.
Now in Bible prophecy, we've talked
about we talk about other
powers and particular
particularly the little horn of Daniel
7 which we describe as a papal
power. It is an anti-Christian
power but it is not the
ultimate anti-Christian power.
The
papacy will be to
Satan what John the Baptist was to
Jesus. John the Baptist was only
preparing the way for
Jesus. In the same
way, the the papacy, the little horn of
Daniel 7 is not the ultimate antichrist.
The ultimate antichrist, the ultimate
individual to put himself in the place
of Christ is Satan
himself. Now, I want you to watch what
the text says because remember, speaking
of this of this king of the north power,
let me go back. Let me go back just a
few slides and I'm going to read Daniel
11:40 again. And notice what the Bible
says here. At the time of the end, at
the time of the end shall the king of
the south push at him and the king of
the north shall come against him like a
whirlwind with chariots and with
horsemen and with many ships. Okay.
So what does it mean then that this
little horn
comes like a whirlwind? What does that
signify? I want you to note with me
Isaiah
66:15. In Isaiah 66:15, we're going to
see something absolutely amazing. Isaiah
66:15 reads, "For behold, the Lord will
come with fire with his
chariots." There we go. The Lord will
come with fire and with his
chariots like
a
whirlwind. Like a what
everyone? Like a
whirlwind to render his anger with fury
and his rebuke with flames of fire. So
we know that when the Lord himself
returns, the Bible says he is coming
like a whirlwind.
He is
coming with a
whirlwind. He's coming with
chariots. How is the the king of the
north described in Daniel 11:40? Just
before Michael stands up, the king of
the north is described as coming like a
whirlwind and with chariots.
So let's talk about these chariots for a
moment because now I want you to
understand here that what we're seeing
is that the Bible is telling us that the
ultimate miracle, the final miracle of
Satan will be a counterfeiting of Jesus
Christ. A counterfeiting of his second
coming. Satan will make it appear that
he is the second coming of Jesus. And
for
unbelievers whom seeing is
believing, this is the miracle above
every other miracle that is going to
bring the whole world together on the
same
page. Listen
y'all, when Satan
comes as Christ, he is not coming alone.
The text says that he's coming with
chariots. The king of the north is
coming with
chariots. What do you mean by chariots,
pastor? Let's go to 2 Kings chapter 6
verse 17. And I want you to note with me
2 Kings chapter 6 and verse 17. The
Bible says, "And Elijah prayed and said,
Lord, I pray thee, open his eyes that he
may see." Elijah is praying that his
servant who who they are surrounded by
the Syrian army, his servant is
petrified. ter is he's he's he's
worrying and Elijah prayed that the
servant's eyes would be open and notice
the next verse or the notice the same
verse rather and the Lord opened the
eyes of the young man and he saw and
behold the mountain was full of horses
and chariots of fire round about
Elijah. What do the chariots and
horses what does that symbolize? Who are
they? These are the
angels. When Satan comes
again, just like the frogs that overtook
the land, they were in the houses, they
were in their beds, they were
everywhere. In the very same way,
beloved, when Satan comes impersonating
Jesus, his
angels, Satan's
angels are going to manifest themselves
as angels of
light, angels from
heaven. And beloved, let me tell you
this. If you think or if
you there's a reason the Bible says it
will be a time of
trouble unlike any other
time in
history. I want you to understand
why it is
because when Satan comes again, he's not
coming alone. He's coming with chariots
and
horsemen, which is going to lead people
to the overwhelming
conclusion that this must be Jesus and
the angels from heaven. Notice again
with me Psalm
68:17. Psalm 68:17, the Bible says, "The
chariots of God are 20,000, even
thousands of angels." Do y'all see this?
The chariots of God are
20,000, even thousands of
angels. These are angels. Satan is
coming with an army of chariots and
horsemen. Angels that will be
pretending to be heavenly angels when in
fact they are demons.
Just as the frogs overtook the land, so
these angels will overtake the land. It
will be an overwhelming experience for
all who are not grounded on the word of
God. If you do not understand the Bible,
this overmastering
delusion will convince
you that this is something of God.
All right. What about the ships? Come
with me to Psalm
107:23. If he's coming with an army of
chariots and an army of ships, we might
say a navy of ships. Well, who is this
navy? What do they represent? Come with
me. Psalm
107:23. Psalm 107 verse 23. The Bible
says
um the Bible says, "They that go down to
the sea in ships, that do business in
the great waters, these see the works of
the Lord and his wonders in the deep."
So, here's what I want you to see
here. Ships are connected with the
deep.
Ships are connected with the deep. the
waters. Now, why is that significant?
Let me show you what the deep symbolizes
in scripture. Come again with me to
Psalm 69 verse one and two. Save me, oh
God, for the waters are coming unto my
soul. I
sink in deep mire where there is no
standing. I am come into deep waters
where the floods overflow me.
What do what does the deep represent
here? The deep represents
death. Let's verify that. Let's verify
that. We're going to go back to the
screen and I want you to notice the
story of Jonah. Jonah chapter 2 verse
1-3. Then Jonah prayed unto the Lord his
God out of the fish's belly and said, "I
cry by reason of mine affliction unto
the Lord. And he heard my he heard me.
Out of the belly of hell, cried I, and
thou heardest my voice. For thou hast
cast me into the deep, in the midst of
the seas, and the floods compassed me
about, and thy billows, all thy billows,
and thy waves passed over me. Now, you
remember that when Jonah was in the
belly of the fish for three days and
three nights in the
deep, that Jesus uses exact example to
talk about his own death.
his own death. Therefore, in fact, in
Romans chapter 10:7, it comes out
clearly and says it. Romans 10:7, notice
what the Bible
says. Romans 10:7, or who or verse 7,
verse 7. Yeah. Or who shall
descend? Who shall descend? Oh boy. Hold
on. Hold on. Let me let me come back.
Let me come
back. There we go. There we go. Who
shall descend into the deep? That is to
bring up Christ again from the dead. Do
you see that? From the dead. Psalm
68:22, the Lord said, "I will bring
again from Bashan. I will bring my
people again from the depths of the
sea." It is a poetical way of speaking
about the
resurrection of the dead.
And in fact, even if you go to
Revelation
17:15, the Bible tells us in Revelation
17 verse verse 15, he saith unto me,
"The waters which thou saw where the
horse siteth are peoples and nations and
multitudes and tongues." Let's put this
all together.
If the sea in one sense represent
peoples, nations, multitudes, and
tongues, but in another sense it
represents the dead, those who have
died, then the army of
ships that Satan is going to
utilize would
represent a
counterfeit resurrection of the dead.
And just as the frogs overtook the land
and they were
everywhere, so beloved, when this
miracle happens, not only is it this
dazzling being who is coming pretending
to be Christ, but to back up his claim
that he is Christ, number one, he will
be accompanied by an army of angels
claiming to be angelic
beings that are coming with Jesus at
second coming along with the
resurrection of the
dead, your dead loved ones, our dead
loved ones claiming that this is really
Jesus. It will be sensory
overload. Which is why, beloved, if you
are used to going by your senses and not
by a thus sayeth the
Lord, you're setting yourself up for
deception. Yes, this is demonic
drama. Just as the frogs overtook the
land, so these three unclean spirits
like frogs coming out out of the mouth
of the dragon, the beast, and the false
prophet are going to overtake the land.
That's why we we often refer to it as an
overwhelming
deception. This is why it is so
important to understand beloved that the
reason God said do not communicate with
the dead. Deuteronomy 18:10, notice what
the Bible says. There shall not be found
among any of you anyone that maketh his
son or his daughter to pass through the
fire, or that uses divination, or an
observer of times, or an enchanter, or a
witch, or a charmer, or a consultant
with familiar spirits, or a
wizard, or a necromancer. For all that
do these things are an abomination unto
the Lord. Why? Because according to
Ecclesiastes 9:5 and 6, the living know
that they shall die, but the dead know
not
anything. Neither have they anymore a
reward, for the memory of them is
forgotten. Let me tell you something,
beloved. When Jesus resurrects his
people, they will be bodily resurrected.
These are not going to be
spirits. These are going to be bodily
resurrected saints. And unless you know
your
Bible, you're going to be
overwhelmed by this
deception. Note again with me. Note
again with me that these unclean spirits
come out of the mouth of the dragon and
out of the mouth of the beast and out of
the mouth of the false prophet. Let's
put it back up on the screen. Revelation
16:13. I saw three unclean spirits like
frogs coming out of the mouth of the
dragon and out of the mouth of the beast
and out of the mouth of the false
prophet. For they are spirits of devils
working miracles which go forth unto the
kings of the of the whole of the earth
and the whole world to gather them to
the great day of God to the battle of
the great day of God Almighty. Why is
this significant?
Remember in Daniel chapter
11, you have the
whirlwind, that's the
air. You have the
chariots and the horsemen running upon
the land. And you have the ships in the
sea, the three unclean spirits. This
this is a
union of land, sea, and air power. Let
me say it again.
It is as if the attack is so
overwhelming. It's coming from the air.
It's coming from the land. It's coming
from the sea. Symbolically speaking. And
beloved, that is significant because
when you look at the beast, watch this.
In Revelation 13:11, the beast that is
spoken about here comes up out of the
sea. Revelation 13:1. And I stood upon
the sand of the sea and saw a beast rise
up out of the sea. We're not going to
even identify this beast for now. We
just just just just follow what I'm
saying here. The there's a beast from
the sea in Revelation 13:11. There's
another beast that comes up out of the
earth having two horns like a lamb and
speaks as a dragon. This is what was
this is the beast known as the false
prophet. He has the horns of a lamb.
That's Jesus. But speaks like a dragon.
He's a false prophet. His his speech is
false. And then you have the dragon.
Revelation uh chapter
12:3. You have the dragon. Note with me.
Here it is on the screen. And there
appeared another wonder in heaven. And
behold, a great red dragon. There it is.
A great red dragon having seven heads
and 10 horns. There is air power, the
dragon in the in the in the in the
heavens. There is sea power, the beast
from the sea. And there is earth power,
the beast from the earth. the the
unclean
spirits will be using these three
elements to help gather the whole world
together under the leadership of this
counterfeit Jesus Christ.
In
fact, in Revelation 18:1, note with me
there, Revelation 18:1, the Bible says,
"And after these things, I saw another
angel come down from heaven having great
power, and the earth was lightened with
his glory, and he cried with a strong
voice, mightily, with a strong voice,
saying, Babylon the great is fallen, is
fallen, and is become what? the
habitation of devils and the hold of
every foul spirit and a cage of every
unclean and hateful bird. The text is
literally telling
us that there is coming a time where
Babylon will be literally
inhabited by devils and
demons. That is not the case now.
Babylon as it exists now has not
completely
fallen. It cannot yet be said that
Babylon is fallen because it is not yet
the habitation of devils. Devils haven't
moved in to planet Earth.
But there is coming a time where that
veil that separates the seen from the
unseen is going to be ripped away and
almost as if you're in a sci-fi movie
except it is not a sci-fi
movie. Demons in disguise or disguised
as angels will come and live among us.
The greatest of them being Lucifer who
is claiming to be Jesus.
Y'all put a one in the chat if you're
following what I'm saying. If this makes
sense. We're demonstrating this strictly
from the
Bible. Note what the Bible says in John
14:1. In John 14:1, the Bible says, "Let
not your heart be troubled. You believe
in God, believe also in me. In my
father's house are many mansions. If it
were not so, I would have told you. I go
to prepare a place for you. And if I go
and prepare a place for you, I will come
again and receive you unto myself, that
where I am, there you may be
also. Where I
am, there you may be
also. Jesus says, when I come again, I'm
not coming to set up a kingdom here on
the earth. I'm coming to take you where
I am.
And this is how we may know that this is
a counterfeit because Jesus doesn't come
to dwell here with us at the second
coming. He says, "I'm coming to take you
that where I am, there you may be also."
In fact, in fact, in 1 Thessalonians
4:16, the Bible says, "For the Lord
himself shall descend from heaven with a
shout, with the voice of the archangel,
and with the trump of God, and the dead
in Christ shall rise first. Then we
which are alive and remain shall be
caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air, not
on the earth, to meet the Lord in the
air, not on the earth. To meet the Lord
in the air, not on the earth. And so
shall we ever what? Be with the Lord.
Just like Jesus said, that you may be
where I am. where I am, you may be there
with me
also. So, how do we know that this is a
counterfeit? Jesus, when he comes again,
he doesn't touch the earth. He stops in
the air. The saints meet him in the air
and he goes, he takes them to heaven
with him. The counterfeit which people
because people do not realize that when
Jesus comes again, he doesn't touch the
ground. When Jesus comes again, he calls
the saints up in the air to meet him.
When Jesus comes again, the saints are
bodily resurrected, not spirits that you
can't touch. And you, you
know,
because many people don't know this,
they are being set up to
receive this
overmastering delusion, this
deception. If y'all with me so far, put
a one in the chat.
We're breaking this down strictly from
scripture. And now I want to show you
what is Satan going to do when he sits
in the temple of God showing himself
that he is God. When all the world has
come together to worship him as God.
What is happening? What why is he doing
this? Come back with me to Revelation
13:3. Revelation 13:3. Notice what the
Bible says here. Revelation 13:3.
The Bible says, "And he doeth great
wonders, so that he maketh fire come
down from heaven on the earth in the
sight of men, and deceive them that
dwell on the earth by the means of those
miracles which he had power to do in the
sight of the beast, saying to them that
dwell on the earth, that they should
make an image to the beast beast, which
had the wound by the sword, and did
live."
Okay. So, what is this talking about?
What is this
fire? What is the purpose of the fire
falling? Why does the Bible use that
terminology? He will cause fire to fall
from the sky. Ah, we got to go back to
another Old Testament story. And that
Old Testament story is a story of Elijah
and the 450 false prophets. Note with me
what the Bible says in First Kings
chapter 18. Now remember remember this
that in this story of Elijah with the
false prophets, they gather together and
they're about to have this contest.
Whichever Elijah is going to pray,
they're going to pray. They're going to
pray to their gods. Elijah is going to
pray to his God. Whichever god answers
by
fire, the text said, "Let him be God."
That was a challenge. Let's see if your
God is a real God or my God is a real
God. And so I want you after the 450
false prophets, they're doing
everything, dancing and whatever,
whatever, and fire doesn't fall. Notice
what happens next. First Kings
18:23. First Kings chapter 18:23, the
Bible says, "Let them therefore," let's
see, here we Let them therefore give us
two bulocks, and let them choose one
bulock for themselves, and cut it in
pieces, and lay it on wood, put no fire
under, and I will dress the other
bulock, and lay it on the on the wood,
and put no fire under it. And ye call
upon the name of your gods, and I will
call on the name of the Lord, and the
God that answers by fire, let him be
God. And all the people answered and
said, "It is well spoken." Verse 36. Um,
so the Bible says after they do all of
this and the false prophets don't get an
answer in verse 36, it came to
pass. There we go. It says, "It came to
pass at the time of the evening
sacrifice that Elijah the prophet came
near and said, Lord God of Abraham,
Isaac, and of Israel, let it be known
this day that thou art God in Israel and
that I am thy servant and that I have
done all these things at thy word. Hear
me, oh Lord. Hear me that this people
may know that thou art the Lord God and
that thou has turned their heart back
again. I want you to note again that
this miracle is designed to turn the
hearts of the people to
God. And so what
happens? Verse 38. Then the fire of the
Lord
fell and consumed the burnt sacrifice
and the wood and the stones and the dust
and licked up the water that was in the
trench. And now watch this. And when all
the people saw it, they fell on their
faces and they said, "The Lord, he is
God. The Lord, he is the God." What's
going on here? This miracle of fire
falling from the sky, this
counterfeit is to
prove that God is
God. What I want you to understand,
beloved, is that this is the very
miracle. It is the frogs of Revelation
chapter 16. It is the king of the north
coming like the whirlwind of Daniel
chapter 11. This is the miracle that
brings the whole world to say he is God.
He is God.
Are y'all with
me? This is the miracle that turns the
heart of the people to this counterfeit
God that leads them to worship. This is
why Revelation 13:4 says this. Let me
read it. Revelation 13 13:4, "And they
worshiped the dragon which gave power
unto the beast. And they worshiped the
beast, saying, Who is like unto the
beast? who is able to make war with him.
Revelation 13:15. And they he had power
to give life unto the image of the
beast, that the image of the beast
should both speak and cause that as many
as would not worship the image of the
beast should
be killed.
Do you guys remember what
happened when Elijah
um after the fire
fell? What happened to the 450 false
prophets? What happened to
them? They were what everybody?
They were
killed. When all the world is convinced
that this is God, but there's a group of
people saying, "Nah, you are not God.
You are the
devil." What? What did you just say
about
Jesus? You just
blasphemed. And what is the punishment
for
blasphemy especially in the face of
Jesus? The punishment will be
death. Whosoever would not worship the
image should be
killed. It is a perversion. The devil's
going to pervert counterfeit the story
of Elijah, a prophet. It's going to be a
false prophet. It's going to be a false
Jesus. And those who refuse to bow and
to say he is
God are going to be punished with a
death
decree. That's what the Bible tells us.
Come on, let's go back to Isaiah 66:15.
And I want you to notice this here.
Isaiah 66:15. And we're almost there,
guys. We are almost finished. Isaiah
66:15. We had read this verse earlier.
It says, "For behold, the Lord will come
with fire and with his
chariots like a
whirlwind to render his anger with fury,
and his rebuke with flames of fire." So,
we've already seen that the devil's
going to try to counterfeit this. For by
fire and by his sword will he plead with
all flesh, and the slain of the Lord
shall be many. This is what the devil's
going to seek to counterfeit. The
devil's going to seek to to plead with
all flesh. I'm Jesus. Come worship me.
Let's see what the rest of the text
says. Verse
17 or verse 18. For I know their works
and their thoughts. It shall come that I
will gather all nations and tongues, and
they shall come and see my glory. Do you
see what Satan is going to try to
counterfeit? This verse is talking about
Jesus, but Satan's going to attempt to
counterfeit Isaiah
66. He wants all the world to
see his
glory and to come and worship. Let's
keep
reading. Let's keep reading. Notice what
the text goes on to say. And I will set
a sign among them. A sign among them.
And I will send those that escape of
them unto the nations to Tarses to P to
Lud and that draw the b the bow to Tubal
and Javant to the aisles a far off that
have not heard of my fame neither have
seen my glory and they shall declare my
glory among the Gentiles. Let me tell
you why. When Jesus comes again, every
eye sees him. That can't happen with
Satan. They're not going to see him at
the same time. So Satan's going to have
to send Satan can't be everywhere at one
time.
So, Satan is going to have to send his
missionaries, his
evangelists, his angels to the whole
world. These are three unclean
spirits that are a counterfeit of
something the Bible calls the three
angels
messages. The three unclean spirits are
going to be gathering the whole world.
While at the same time, the three angels
messages found in Revelation chapter 14
are going to be gathering all those who
are faithful to Jesus. Two different
messages. Two different
messages. Notice what Isaiah 66 goes on
to say. This gets very interesting,
beloved. If it if you're not interested
yet, watch this. Isaiah
66 verse 20. Verse 20. And they shall
bring, here we go, and they shall bring
all your brethren for an offering unto
the Lord, out of all nations upon
horses, and in chariots, and in litters,
and upon mules, and upon swift beasts to
my holy mountain in Jerusalem, sayith
the Lord, as the children of Israel
bring an offering in a clean vessel unto
the house of the Lord. This is exactly
what the devil's going to attempt to
counterfeit here on earth. He's going to
try to get all the world all the
world, all the
world to come and worship
him. And
then then verse
21, and I will also take of them
priests for uh for for them take for
them priests and for Levites, say the
Lord. Hm. Priests and
Levites. He's going to call them to be
kings and priests with him for a
thousand
years. Do y'all catch this? We're going
to come to that in a moment. But I want
you to note how the devil is literally
seeking to counterfeit prophecy, but
twist it so that the world will worship
him. Let's keep reading.
I will take for them for priests and for
and for Levites. For as the new heavens
and the new earth which I shall make
shall remain before me, sayeth the Lord,
so shall your seed in your name remain.
And it shall come to pass that from one
new moon to another, and from one
Sabbath to another shall all flesh come
before me to worship. Here's what I need
y'all to understand.
The devil is going to make it so that
every the whole world comes before him
to
worship and they will think they're
worshiping
Jesus. And his special
sign will be
Sabbath to Sabbath.
And we're not going to get into that
now, but I just need you to know that
just as it's a counterfeit Jesus, it
will be a counterfeit
Sabbath. Note the next
verse. Note the next verse. And they
shall go forth and look upon the
carcasses of the men that have
transgressed against
me. Do y'all see this?
The devil's going to make it so that the
righteous are considered wicked and the
wicked are considered righteous. The
wicked will be the priests and the
Levites that are serving the quote
unquote Lord while the while the
righteous will be deemed as the men that
have transgressed against this Jesus.
In Revelation chapter 20, in Revelation
chapter 20, the Bible says, "And I saw
an angel come down from heaven, having
the key of the bottomless pit in his
hand, and a great chain. And he laid
hold on the dragon, that old serpent,
which is the devil and Satan, and bound
him a thousand years, and cast him into
the bottomless pit, and shut him up, and
set a seal upon him, that he should
deceive the nations no more, till the
thousand years should be fulfilled." And
after that he must be loose a little
season. And I saw thrones, and they sat
upon them, and judgment was given unto
them. And I saw the souls of them that
were beheaded for the witness of Jesus
and for the word of God, and which had
not worshiped the beast, neither his
image, neither had received his mark
upon their foreheads or in their hands.
And they lived and reigned with Christ a
thousand years. I want y'all to
understand that this this is what the
Bible describes as the millennium, the
1,000 years. And the Bible tells us that
in the millennium, the saints will spend
it with Jesus in heaven.
But Satan will make it appear that the
millennium is taking place here on
earth. So that when he comes, he's going
to say to the world, "The millennium has
begun. This is the reign of peace, and
everyone who is against this reign of
peace is against me, and they ought to
be put to death. They ought to be put to
death." Just like in First Kings
18:39, when all the people saw it, they
fell on their faces, and they said, "The
Lord, he is God. The Lord, he is the
God." And Elijah said unto them, "Take
the prophets of Baal. Let not one of
them escape." And they took them, and
Elijah brought them down to the brook
Kidron, and slew them there. This is
going to be a counterfeit, beloved, of
that story.
All those who refuse to worship this
Jesus, a death decree will be issued
against
them. And now you can begin to
understand why Revelation 12 says these
words. Revelation 12:1 17, the dragon
was wroth with the woman and went to
make war with the remnant of her seed,
which keep the commandments of God and
have the testimony of Jesus Christ. This
this counterfeit miracle will be
targeted towards those who refuse to
worship Jesus, this Jesus.
So the question is, how do I
stand in the midst of such an
overwhelming delusion that will take the
world by storm? How do I stand? Let me
show you. Um, let me show you and then
then we'll close up. Revelation 15:2,
please note what the Bible says here.
Revelation 15:2, I saw an
angel. Uh, I'm sorry. I saw as it were a
sea of
glass, a sea of glass, my slide, sea of
glass mingled with fire. Them that had
gotten the victory over the beast and
over his image and over his mark and
over the number of his name stand on the
sea of glass, having the hearts of God.
We see here that there will be in fact a
people who have the victory over
everything that these three unclean
spirits are going to attempt to do. Why
do they have the victory? Let me let me
suggest to you number one that they
stood on the word of God. The Bible
says, "Therefore, whosoever he hearth
these sayings of mine and doeth them, I
will liken him unto a wise man which
built his house upon a rock. And the
rain descended, and the floods came, and
the winds blew, and beat upon that
house, and it fell not, for it was
founded on a rock. And everyone who
hearth these sayings of mines, and doeth
them not, shall be likened unto a
foolish man which built his house on the
sand. And the rain descended, and the
floods came, and the winds blew, and
beat upon that house, and it fell, and
great was the fall of it. May I suggest
to you that the word of God, you must
make it your ultimate guide, not your
emotions, not your feelings. Because if
you depend on emotions and feelings, if
you allow your emotions and feelings to
get the best of you, and beloved, listen
to me. Sometimes we can allow our
emotions and our feelings to get the
best of us. when today as I'm g as I'm
preaching and the power kicked out. Oh
boy, I I was
frustrated. I was like,
why? Why? Why now? I have a message to
preach. This message is going to be
powerful. Why now?
And beloved, sometimes our
emotions can get the best of
us and every one of us have to deal with
it. How
Lord, how can I train? How can I give
myself so fully to you that my
emotions will not get the best of me?
Because if you allow your emotions to
get the best of you, I'm telling
you, when this thing
comes, and the glory that you see is
unlike anything you have ever seen
before. Yeah.
It will draw
you in a way nothing has ever drawn you
before. And unless we have unless we're
standing on the word of
God, unless we're standing on the word
of
God, this is why Jesus said, "If it were
possible, even the very elect would be
deceived. Do not allow your senses to
overwhelm you." The Bible says in second
2 second Timothy chapter 2:15, "Study to
show thyself approved unto God a workman
that needeth not be ashamed, rightly
dividing the word of truth." You have
study the word of God. Some people say
you don't have to study as long as you
know Jesus. Listen
y'all. The reason Jesus gave us the
word
is because precisely because it is the
word that guides our path. It is the
word that that shows us the way in which
we should
walk. 2 Corinthians 5:17 says, "For we
walk by faith, not by sight." If you're
going to trust your sight over faith,
you're going to end up falling to this
overmastering
delusion. Remember, remember what Jesus
said. Matthew 24:2, he said, "Behold, I
told you before, wherefore, if they
shall say unto you, if they shall say
unto you, behold, he's in the desert,
believe it not. He's in the secret
chamber.
Go not
forth. For as lightning cometh out of or
as lightning shineth out of the east and
cometh even unto the west, so shall the
coming of the son of man be. He
literally says, except those days be
shortened, no flesh shall be saved. This
is
how deep this time is going to
be. And according to Jeremiah 12:5,
Jeremiah 12:5, the Bible tells us, let
me just just skipping through my slides
now. If thou has run with the footmen,
and they have wearied thee, then how can
you contend with horses? And if in the
land of peace, wherein you trusted, they
wearied thee, then how will thou do in
the swelling of the Jordan? Beloved,
listen to me. The little trials we face
now will be nothing compared to what we
will face then, if we happen to be alive
in this
time. And the Bible says, if the little
things overwhelm
us, if the little things overwhelm
us, how are we going to do when this
sensory overload takes the whole world
by
storm? And I that's no pun on
words. That's no pun on words. Or I
should say, yeah, pun intended.
How will you do when this storm hits the
whole world? The Bible says in Amos 3:3,
"Can two walk together except they be
agreed?" Can two walk together except
they be agreed? Let me say this. Let me
say this.
If there is anything in
you that Satan has in
him, when you see him, you going you're
going to be drawn to him.
When Jesus said, "The prince of this
world cometh and has nothing in me."
There was
nothing in him that was attracted to
Satan that could be attracted to Satan.
Remember, when Satan appears to Jesus in
the wilderness, he's appearing to him as
an angel of
light. If there is stuff in your
heart that is unclean, so remember what
we call these spirits. These were
unclean spirits.
unclean is attracted to unclean. And
what God is demonstrating here in this
time is that only those who are
unclean will be attracted to these
unclean frogs, to these unclean spirits.
So, so God is showing us, he's telling
us, listen, pray to get the unclean out
of
you. Pray to get Christ in you and the
unclean out of you.
Here's our closing text. It's a parable
really, but I think it's
significant for our closing
text. It's Luke 11 24. And it says this,
"When the unclean spirit is gone out of
a man, he walketh through dry places
seeking rest and findeth none. And he
saith, I will return unto my house once
I came out." And when he cometh, he
findeth it swept and
garnished. It's
empty. What does he do? He goes and
takes to him seven other spirits more
wicked than
himself. And they enter in and dwell
there. And the state, the last state of
that man is worse
than the first.
The enemy of souls is
seeking to let out these unclean
spirits into our
homes, up in our beds, up in our
food. The time is not it's not come yet,
but it is coming.
And the only way to be safe,
beloved, is to have Jesus in your
heart. Because if he's not in your
heart and those frogs come trying to get
into your house, they're going to find a
way in. And they're not coming
alone. Won't just be one
frog. It'll be legions of them.
So our prayer today, our
prayer, my
prayer is that our prayer will be
Lord remove from me
every unclean thing.
Let Satan have nothing in
me so that should I be alive when this
time
comes that I will not there will be
nothing in me that is drawn to him
nothing in me that responds to him.
Beloved, we got to be careful. If if you
respond, if if if corrupt people draw
you
now, if unclean people mesmerize you
now, if you're just attracted in some
strange way to people who who do not
have the spirit of God in them, and you
just like, yeah, you
know, just imagine what it'll be
like when Satan himself appears as
Jesus. Lord, help
us to not be among
those that will be deceived by these
unclean
spirits. May that be our prayer.
May it be our prayer that we will study
the word of God to show ourselves
approved and that we will allow Christ
the hope of
glory to dwell in
us to keep us
safe and to keep our homes our
homes
barricaded from these unclean spirits.
Heavenly Father, thank you for listening
to us or thank you for listening to our
prayer. Thank you Lord for speaking to
your people
today. And Lord, I
um I just ask Lord that you would help
us to to overcome
um our feelings, our emotions, Lord.
Lord, I ask that you would forgive me,
Lord, for just my frustration, Lord,
with the power going out. And it seemed
like everything that could have gone
wrong with
this message went wrong with
it. Lord,
please humble us so that we see our our
ways. we see the things that we need
um to rid ourselves
of that we might be ready when you come
again to receive
us. Please Lord, help us to put faith
over
[Music]
feeling. Faith over
emotion. Your word over anything our
senses tell us.
Thank you Lord for hearing and answering
this prayer because we ask it in Jesus
name. Amen. And
amen. Uh thank you all for uh tuning
back in. Um wow, we almost had as as as
many as we had when the thunderstorm
came and kicked us all out. So
um uh shut the power off. So, um, we're
going to put the link in the, uh, the
link for the slides in the chat. I think
we've just put it in. So, if you want to
take this, uh, sermon and share it, if
you want to listen again, if you're an
evangelist, if you're doing a series and
you've never preached this before, um,
I've just given you everything that you
need to preach this message from the
Bible and the Bible only. Um, but above
that, above all that, may we live this
thing out and may we be ready uh for
when this time comes and we we we just
uh pray that uh none of us will be found
wanting in that time. All right, may God
bless you. We're going to put the link
to the altar live. I don't know if we're
still going to be doing the altar live.
I know that it is way later than we
typically finish, but
um uh we'll put the link in and um we'll
see how the Lord leads. May God bless
you and may God keep you.
Amen. Thank you for joining us today. If
this is your first time worshiping with
us, please check out our website at
livingmana.urch. We are not just here
for Sabbath service. We have weekly
programming too that covers mental
health, physical health, weekly prayer
service, financial health, and proving
the existence of God. It is our desire
that our programming will continue to
bless you. Please continue to pray for
us as we fulfill God's mission to go
into all the world with the gospel of
Jesus Christ.
[Music]